Antonio Silva

Web Developer



About

A highly skilled developer with experience in developing with Javascript, React, Redux, NodeJS, PostgreSQL, HTML, CSS. Using Scrum for agile methodologies and Git & GitHub for version control.

Strong background in problem solving, strategic planning and team leadership. Holds a Bachelor's degree in Tech Engineering and a Full Stack Developer certification.

Experience

Position: Technical Support.
Place: Guanajuato Goverment.
Dates: October 2015 to Present.

- Technical support to users, specialized in repair, maintenance, configuration and installation of Microsoft Office, Adobe package, AntiMalware, Lotus Notes, ERP Mapics, Local server files, etc.
- Maintained a user satisfaction rating of 100% year over year by providing responsive tech support to users.
- Boosted monthly productivity by 60% by preventing maintenance to organize and track bugs in the first semester of 2022.

Position: Web Developer.

Place: SoyHenry, Argentinian tech firm.

Dates: August 2022 to Present.

• Project: Marketplace

- Features: User authentication with AuthO, payment gateway with mercadoPago, dark/light mode, combined filters, minimalist design, search by name, Local Storage, Dashboard admin, Reviews/score.
- Technologies: Javascript, React, Redux, Chakra JS, NodeJS, PostgreSQL, Sequelize. <u>Live demo</u>

Project: Landing Page

- Features: Fluid and user-friendly interactivity, minimalist and responsive design
- Technologies: Javascript, React, Tailwind Live demo

Contact



Portfolio



Github



Linkedin

- asilvazavala@gmail.com
- +52 456-114-8433

Skills

- Backend: Express, Node JS, Sequelize, PostgreSQL.
- Frontend: Javascript, HTML, CSS, React, Redux.
- Others: Git, Github.

Education

Carrer: Technology

Engineering

Place: De la Salle University

Dates: 2010-2014

Professional license: 9715622

Languages: Spanish: Native

English: (C1) Certificate